And man, it's still show.
Hendrick Lamar has started off the week with a verse.
Okay, he comes for Drake and J. Cole
on Future and Metro Boomin' song like that.
If I'm keeping it like all the way honest.
I didn't know it was a diss record until the last line.
I thought he was just talking spicy,
but I don't really think it was a diss record.
No, it is a diss record.
Once he says it, yeah, it's a diss record.
It's been broken down, yes.
He's making correlations between lines that,
like direct lines that J. Cole says.
Oh, okay, it went over my head then
because I only got that one little line.
Listen, I had to watch breakdowns.
I had to watch breakdowns on the internet.
I call Kendrick Lamar the Cornel West of rap
because sometimes Cornel West be talking and you like,
I feel like what you're saying is important.
I just can't understand what you're saying.
You know, I think that he appears like every four years
just to be like, oh, y'all thought I was gone, you know?
And it is like, we are approaching Easter.
So it's very like back like Jordan wearing the four five.
You know what I'm saying?
He's like, I'm gonna hit y'all
with a Resurrection Sunday on Palm Sunday.
I mean, that's essentially the energy.
What do you think?
Do you think K-Dot killed it?
Or, you know, do you think he needs
to take another stab at it?
And also, you know, do you think the original rap
was good from J. Cole and Drake?
Hit me up.
1-855-MAND-8.
That's 1-855-262-6328.
We up.